{
    "subject": "resource/Marisa_Pavan",
    "predicate": "property/children",
    "object": "Patrick Aumont",
    "human_readable": "Marisa Pavan has a child named Patrick Aumont.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786992073059082,
            "question": "Is Patrick Aumont related to Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9786992073059082,
            "question": "Is Patrick Aumont related to Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950674533843994,
            "question": "What is the name of Marisa Pavan's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8864438533782959,
            "question": "Name one of Marisa Pavan's children."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843880295753479,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of a child belonging to Marisa Pavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8729820251464844,
            "question": "Who is the parent of Patrick Aumont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612818717956543,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Marisa Pavan and Patrick Aumont?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8481296896934509,
            "question": "Who is Patrick Aumont's parent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8457413911819458,
            "question": "Does Marisa Pavan have children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6275889277458191,
            "question": "Who is Patrick Aumont's mother?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marisa Pavan has a child named Patrick Aumont.",
            "html": "dbpedia_671_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Marisa Pavan have children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_671_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Patrick Aumont's parent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_671_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Marisa Pavan and Patrick Aumont?",
            "html": "dbpedia_671_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_671_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Jean-Pierre Aumont was married to Marisa Pavan and had two sons, Jean-Claude and Patrick Aumont. This implies that Marisa Pavan is indeed the mother of Patrick Aumont."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Marisa Pavan had two children, Jean-Claude and Patrick Aumont. Therefore, the triple \"Marisa Pavan has a child named Patrick Aumont\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}